[{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":17059,"timeElapsed":256626},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":13163,"timeElapsed":269795},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980481874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":11979,"timeElapsed":281777},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":9473,"timeElapsed":291253},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":8537,"timeElapsed":299792},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":7317,"timeElapsed":307111},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980513342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6131,"timeElapsed":313245},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":12480,"timeElapsed":325727},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980531608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":5782,"timeElapsed":331510},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":45655,"timeElapsed":378938},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6948,"timeElapsed":385889},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3928,"timeElapsed":389818},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4657,"timeElapsed":394481},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4760,"timeElapsed":399242},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980602214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2872,"timeElapsed":402117},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4059,"timeElapsed":406178},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4109,"timeElapsed":410289},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5211,"timeElapsed":415502},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7049,"timeElapsed":423991},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3409,"timeElapsed":427401},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7502,"timeElapsed":434905},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":438465},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4059,"timeElapsed":442525},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980645396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2772,"timeElapsed":445299},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5297,"timeElapsed":450597},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4443,"timeElapsed":455042},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4812,"timeElapsed":459855},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":12682,"timeElapsed":473726},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4076,"timeElapsed":477804},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4275,"timeElapsed":482081},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":484722},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":6400,"timeElapsed":491123},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3975,"timeElapsed":495100},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2488,"timeElapsed":497590},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3508,"timeElapsed":501100},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980704372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":504275},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":7202,"timeElapsed":512397},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":514687},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980717692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2906,"timeElapsed":517595},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5245,"timeElapsed":522841},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2956,"timeElapsed":525799},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3575,"timeElapsed":529376},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":531565},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":534222},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980737494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3173,"timeElapsed":537397},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":10911,"timeElapsed":549413},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1702,"timeElapsed":551117},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980754122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2906,"timeElapsed":554025},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":556315},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5045,"timeElapsed":561361},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1787,"timeElapsed":563150},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980766473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3224,"timeElapsed":566375},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980769046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2572,"timeElapsed":568949},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980773825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4777,"timeElapsed":573728},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5664,"timeElapsed":580363},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1836,"timeElapsed":582201},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3223,"timeElapsed":585426},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980788498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2973,"timeElapsed":588401},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980791656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3157,"timeElapsed":591559},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2137,"timeElapsed":593698},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":595987},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980798424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2339,"timeElapsed":598327},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818579,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":20153,"timeElapsed":618482},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3707,"timeElapsed":622191},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980832634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":8970,"timeElapsed":632537},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1902,"timeElapsed":634441},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980837947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3407,"timeElapsed":637850},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980841105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":641008},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2005,"timeElapsed":643014},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846387,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3274,"timeElapsed":646290},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855727,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9338,"timeElapsed":655630},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980859339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3610,"timeElapsed":659241},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980862312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2972,"timeElapsed":662215},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980864919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2606,"timeElapsed":664822},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7369,"timeElapsed":676404},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980880345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3842,"timeElapsed":680248},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2338,"timeElapsed":682587},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2238,"timeElapsed":684827},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":688386},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980892060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3574,"timeElapsed":691963},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4794,"timeElapsed":696759},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980900583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3725,"timeElapsed":700485},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980904727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4142,"timeElapsed":704630},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980914236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":8421,"timeElapsed":714139},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980916859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2621,"timeElapsed":716762},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980923092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6231,"timeElapsed":722995},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2356,"timeElapsed":725353},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980928943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3491,"timeElapsed":728846},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980936947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8003,"timeElapsed":736850},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980940807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3858,"timeElapsed":740710},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980945970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":5161,"timeElapsed":745873},{"subjectID":"e5vyyb269n","prolificID":"5b5a822e1ad8270001c4f28d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26386594cbbaafd6a4d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980949147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3175,"timeElapsed":749050}]